Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings and Dom Baron Chant Recordings
Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings
- Toscanini recordings
  - Sinfonia No. 7 [Symphony No. 7 in A Major, op. 92] - Mvt. I & II - Beethoven; Lenor Obertura No. 2 [Leonore - Overture No. 2] - Beethoven, hupka_2593; Record # ND5-MM-4406 & 4408; Mx # 72B & 73B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sing, Smile, Slumber (Sérénade) - Gounod, 4/21/1916; hupka_3920; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Six Songs, op. 68, No. 2 - Feldeinsamkeit - Brahms, hupka_2360; D7-RB-568-1; Used for broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Six Songs, op. 68, No. 2 - Feldeinsamkeit - Brahms, hupka_4005; IRCC-62-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Six Songs, op. 97, No. 5 - Komm bald - Brahms, hupka_1411; IRCC-62-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Skaters Waltz - Émile Waldteufel (Part 1), 6/25/1944; hupka_1331; D5-TC-261-1; Unpublished; Shellac disc
  - The Skaters' Waltz - Émile Waldteufel (Pt. 1), hupka_3331; D5-RC-549-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Skaters' Waltz - Émile Waldteufel (Pt. 1), hupka_3332; D5-RC-549-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Skaters' Waltz - Émile Waldteufel (Pt. 2), hupka_3333; D5-RC-550-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Skaters Waltz - Émile Waldteufel (Part 2), 6/25/1944; hupka_1332; D5-TC-262-1B; Unpublished; Shellac disc
  - The Skaters' Waltz - Émile Waldteufel (Pt. 2), hupka_3334; D5-RC-550-2A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Skaters' Waltz - Émile Waldteufel (Pt. 2), hupka_3337; D5-RC-550-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sleeping Beauty Waltz - Tchaikovsky, hupka_1367; D7-RC-7980-2A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [Smetana, Humperdinck, Wagner, Beethoven, Brahms, Waldteufe, Kabalevsky], hupka_4152; Sides 7 &8; E3-RP-5206 & 5207; VinylDisc
    The Moldau - Bed?ich Smetana; Hänsel und Gretel - Prelude - Engelbert Humperdinck; Die Walküre - Ride of the Valkyries - Wagner; Coriolan Overture - Beethoven; Four Hungarian Dances, Nos. 1, 17, 20, 21 - Brahms; Skaters Waltz - Emile Waldteufel; Colas Breugnon - Overture - Kabalevsky
  - Soiz paieu - Georges Hüe, hupka_0930; Serial # 4209-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Somewhere a voice is calling - Arthur F. Tate, lyricist - Eileen Newton, hupka_3504; B-15419; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sonata in A, Sonata in E - Scarlatti, hupka_3635; D6-RC-6411-3A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sonata in B minor - Scarlatti, hupka_3636; D6-RC-7966-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sonata in E and Sonata in G - Domenico Scarlatti, hupka_1294; D6-RC-6410-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sonata in F, Sonata in G - Scarlatti, hupka_3634; D6-RC-6410-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sonata, op. 83, No. 7 - Mvt. I - Prokofieff, 12/8/1955; hupka_2284; Shellac disc
  - Sonata, op. 83, No. 7 - Mvt. II & III - Prokofieff, 12/8/1955; hupka_2283; Shellac disc
  - Song of the Volga Boathen, 9/18/1942; hupka_2507; OEA 6162-1; "very bad pressing: weak; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Soona Will Be Done - spiritual, hupka_3008; Serial # D6-RB-2377-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Soona Will Be Done - spiritual, hupka_3024; Serial # D6-RB-2377-3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sosarme - Handel, hupka_1967; AC-6382-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sospiri miei, andate ove vi marido - Alberto Bimboni, 3/28/1913; hupka_2605; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sospiri miei, andate ove vi marido - Alberto Bimboni, 3/28/1913; hupka_3518; Cat # 64333; B-1303-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sounds of the Earth, hupka_3434; 4194-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Spanish Song - Sebastián Yradier, 1908; hupka_1973; C-6022; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Spring - George Henschel; Year's at the Spring - H.H.A. Beach [author for both - Robert Browning], [05/18/1908]; hupka_1014; Seial # IRCC-194-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Stabat Mater - Cujus animam - Rossini, circa 1937-1949; hupka_1940; 13588-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Stabat Mater - Inflammatus et accensus - Rossini, hupka_0864; Spelled "Ruszcowska" on item; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Stabat Mater - Pro peccatis - Rossini, hupka_0809; Serial # IRCC-81-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [Ständchen] Serenade - Richard Strauss [author - Adolf Friedrich von Schack], [11/19/1904]; hupka_2972; IRCC-139-B; Serial # B-1950; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Star Spangled Banner, 3/19/1942; hupka_2848; Record # 073220-1; Shellac disc
  - The Star Spangled Banner, 3/19/1942; hupka_2970; Record # 073220-1; Shellac disc
  - The Star Spangled Banner, 3/19/1942; hupka_3116; Record # 073220-2; Shellac disc
  - The Star Spangled Banner, 3/19/1942; hupka_3238; Record # 073220-2; Shellac disc
  - The Stars and Stripes Forever - Sousa, 5/25/1945; hupka_1813; Record # D5-RC-438-1A; Shellac disc
  - Stella del Nord - La, la, la (Catarina's Aria) - Meyerbeer, circa 1903-1915; hupka_3829; HO-522-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - String Octet in E flat Major, op. 20 - Mendelssohn, 3/30/1947; hupka_3093; Pre-concert announcement; Shellac disc
  - String Octet in E flat Major, op. 20; Symphony No. 5, op. 107 - Mendelssohn, 3/29/1947; hupka_2810; Sides 6 & 8; Rehearsal for 03/30/47 broadcast?; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - String Octet in E flat Major, op. 20; Symphony No. 5, op. 107 - Mendelssohn, 3/29/1947; hupka_2813; Sides 5 & 7; Rehearsal for 03/30/47 broadcast?; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - String Octet in E flat Major, op. 20; Symphony No. 5, op. 107 - Mendelssohn, 3/29/1947; hupka_2814; Sides 2 & 4; Rehearsal for 03/30/47 broadcast?; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - String Octet in E flat Major, op. 20; Symphony No. 5, op. 107 - Mendelssohn, 3/29/1947; hupka_2815; Sides 1 & 3; Rehearsal for 03/30/47 broadcast?; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - String Quartet No. 16 in F Major, op. 135 - Lento assai - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/25/1939; hupka_1456; Studio 8-H Broadcast; Shellac disc
  - String Quartet No. 16 in F Major, op. 135 - Lento assai - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 11/25/1939; hupka_1457; Studio 8-H Broadcast; Shellac disc
  - String Quartet No. 16 in F Major, op. 135 - Vivace - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/25/1939; hupka_1458; Studio 8-H Broadcast; Shellac disc
  - Sulla bocca amorosa - Richard Barthelemy, circa 1903-1908; hupka_1020; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sur le lac - Henri Bemberg, hupka_0917; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sur les cimes - Georges Hüe, [lyricist - A.L. Hettich], 1/11/1912; hupka_1250; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Swans - A. Walter Kramer, lyricist - Sara Teasdale, 4/26/1923; hupka_2727; A-28613; 1081-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Sweet Adeline; Fix Up the Spare Room Mother, hupka_3061; Shellac disc
  - Sweet Thoughts of Home - Julian Edwards, 1/3/1906; hupka_4071; Serial # 85092; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony in D - Mvt. I & IV - Luigi Cherubini, 3/22/1947; hupka_2859; Rehearsal; Side 10; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony in D - Mvt. I, II, III - Luigi Cherubini, 3/22/1947; hupka_2860; Rehearsal; Sides 4 & 9; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony in D - Mvt. IV - Luigi Cherubini, 3/22/1947; hupka_2863; Rehearsal; Sides 6 & 8; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony in D - Mvt. IV - Luigi Cherubini; Loreley - Dance of the Nymphs - Alfredo Catalani; Fountains of Rome - Respighi, 3/22/1947; hupka_2864; Rehearsal; Sides 5 & 7; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. [?] in E flat - Mvt. III Menuetto - Mozart, 12/18/1920; hupka_3386; Toscanini's First Recording; Piece is either Mozart's 19th or 39th symphony; Cat # 6303-A; Serial # C-24738-4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. [?] in E flat - Mvt. IV Finale - Mozart, 12/18/1920; hupka_3387; Toscanini's First Recording; Piece is either Mozart's 19th or 39th symphony; Cat # 6303-B; Serial # C-24740-3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 1 in C Major, op. 21, Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major, op. 55, Fidelio - Overture - Beethoven, 10/28/1969; hupka_2496; # 037995-1; Part 4 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 10.28.1969 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 1 in C Major, op. 21, Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major, op. 55, Fidelio - Overture - Beethoven, 10/28/1969; hupka_2497; # 037995-1; Part 4 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 10.28.1969 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 1 in C Major, op. 21, Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major, op. 55, Fidelio - Overture - Beethoven, 10/28/1969; hupka_2498; # 037996-1 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 10.28.1969 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 1 in C Major, op. 21 - Beethoven, hupka_0671; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 1 in C Major, op. 21 - Mvt. I & II - Beethoven, hupka_2492; # 037993-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 1 in C Major, op. 21 - Mvt. III & IV - Beethoven, hupka_2493; # 037994-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 1 in C Major, op. 21 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven, 3/30/1921; hupka_3388; Serial # C-25119-4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 1 in C Major, op. 21, Symphony No. 8 in F Major, op. 93 - Beethoven, 10/21/1944; hupka_2968; Rehearsal; Includes Toscanini's comments on the rehearsal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor - Mvt. III & IV - Brahms, 5/6/1940; hupka_4163; #MS 050418-1; VinylDisc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor - Mvt. IV - Brahms (conc.), 5/6/1940; hupka_4164; #MS 050419-1; VinylDisc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. I - Brahms (conclusion), 5/6/1940; hupka_3687; Record # 048851-1;"Not fit to use; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. I - Brahms (Part 1), 5/6/1940; hupka_3663; Record # 048849-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. I - Brahms (Part 2), 5/6/1940; hupka_3675; Record # 048850-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. II - Brahms (conclusion), 5/6/1940; hupka_3711; Record # 048853-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. II - Brahms (conclusion), 5/6/1940; hupka_3723; Record # 048853-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. II - Brahms (Part 2), 5/6/1940; hupka_3699; Record # 048852-1;"Not fit to use"; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. III - Brahms, 5/6/1940; hupka_3735; Record # 048854-1;"Not fit to use; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. IV - Brahms, 5/6/1940; hupka_3785; Record # 048858-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (Part 1), 3/10/1941; hupka_3455; Record # 062540-3A; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (Part 1), 5/6/1940; hupka_3747; Record # 048855-1;"Not fit to use; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (Part 1), 5/6/1940; hupka_3759; Record # 048856-1;"Not fit to use; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in C minor, op. 68 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (Part 3), 5/6/1940; hupka_3773; Record # 048857-1; Shellac disc
  - [Symphony No. 1 in D (Classical), op. 25 - Prokofiev; Double Concerto in A minor, op. 102 - Brahms; Die Nacht - Strong; Parsifal - Good Friday Spell - Wagner; Die Meistersinger von Nürnberg - Prelude to Act I - Wagner], 10/23/1939 or[10/21/1939]; hupka_2914; Part 4; 037995-1; Tracks on item come from this broadcast, but do not include all titles listed; Item says that tracks come from 10/23 broadcast, but no broadcast occurred on this date - the pieces from the 10/21 broadcast have been listed; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 1 in D Major, D. 82 - Schubert, hupka_2069; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 1 in D Major, D. 82 - Schubert, hupka_2072; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Beethoven, 11/4/1939; hupka_1833; 043541-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Beethoven, 11/4/1939; hupka_1834; 043545-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/4/1939; hupka_1829; 043544-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/4/1939; hupka_1832; 043540-1A; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 12/19/1944; hupka_3592; D4-RC-565-1A; Recording session at studio 8-H; Not released; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 12/19/1944; hupka_3593; D4-RC-566-1; Recording session at studio 8-H; Not released; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/4/1939; hupka_1830; 043543-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/4/1939; hupka_1831; 043542-1; cracked; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 12/19/1944; hupka_3594; D4-RC-567-1; Recording session at studio 8-H; Not released; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 12/19/1944; hupka_3595; D4-RC-568-1B; Recording session at studio 8-H; Not released; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 12/19/1944; hupka_3596; D4-RC-568-1C; Recording session at studio 8-H; Not released; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 12/19/1944; hupka_3597; D4-RC-569-1; Recording session at studio 8-H; Not released; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. III - Beethoven, 11/4/1939; hupka_3394; Record # 043546-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. III - Beethoven, hupka_3620; D4-4C-570-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. III - Beethoven, hupka_3621; D4-RC-570-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven, 11/4/1939; hupka_3516; Record # 043547-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven, hupka_3622; D4-RC-571-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven, hupka_3623; D4-RC-571-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven (Pt. 2), hupka_3616; D4-RC-572-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 36 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven (Pt. 2), hupka_3617; D4-RC-572-2A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. I - Brahms, 3/9/1947; hupka_1706; D8-RC-631-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. I - Brahms (Pt. 2), 3/9/1947; hupka_1707; D8-RC-632-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. I - Brahms (Pt. 3), 3/9/1947; hupka_1708; D8-RC-633-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. II - Brahms (Pt. 1), 3/9/1947; hupka_1709; D8-RC-634-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. II - Brahms (Pt. 2), 3/9/1947; hupka_1710; D8-RC-635-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. III - Brahms, 3/9/1947; hupka_1711; D8-RC-636-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. IV - Brahms, hupka_2109; 26; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (conc.), 3/9/1947; hupka_1713; D8-RC-638-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (conc.), 3/9/1947; hupka_1714; D8-RC-638-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 2 in D Major, op. 73 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (Pt. 1), 3/9/1947; hupka_1712; D8-RC-637-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D, op. 73 - Mvt. I - Brahms (conclusion), 3/9/1947; hupka_2408; Record # D8-RC-633-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D, op. 73 - Mvt. I - Brahms (Part 1), 3/9/1947; hupka_2384; Record # D8-RC-631-1A; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D, op. 73 - Mvt. I - Brahms (Part 2), 3/9/1947; hupka_2396; Record # D8-RC-632-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D, op. 73 - Mvt. II - Brahms (Part 1), 3/9/1947; hupka_2420; Record # D8-RC-634-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D, op. 73 - Mvt. II - Brahms (Part 2), 3/9/1947; hupka_2432; Record # D8-RC-635-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D, op. 73 - Mvt. IV - Brahms, 3/9/1947; hupka_2444; Record # D8-RC-637-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 2 in D, op. 73 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (Part 2), 3/9/1947; hupka_2456; Record # D8-RC-638-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. 1 - Beethoven, 11/5/1944; hupka_0276; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (conc.), 1950?; hupka_2799; D9-RC-2043-2A; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 1950?; hupka_2763; D9-RC-2040-2B; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 1950?; hupka_2775; D9-RC-2041-2B; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 1950?; hupka_2787; D9-RC-2042-2; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (conc.), 1950?; hupka_2847; D9-RC-2047-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 1950?; hupka_2811; D9-RC-2044-2; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 1950?; hupka_2823; D9-RC-2045-2; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 1950?; hupka_2835; D9-RC-2046-1A; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. III - Beethoven, hupka_2861; D9-RC-2048-3A; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven (conc.), hupka_2897; D9-RC-2051-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven (Pt. 1), hupka_2873; D9-RC-2049-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major (Eroica), op. 55 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven (Pt. 2), hupka_2885; D9-RC-2050-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major, op. 55 - Mvt. III - Beethoven, 10/28/1969; hupka_2499; # 037997-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major, op. 55 (Eroica) - Mvt. IV - Beethoven, hupka_3638; Cat # 17858-S; Serial # CS043539; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 3 in E flat Major, op. 55 (Eroica) - Mvt. IV - Beethoven, hupka_3760; Cat # 17858-S; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 3 in F Major, op. 90 - Brahms, hupka_2991; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 3 in F Major, op. 90 - Brahms, 12/20/1942; hupka_3125; Rehearsal?; VinylDisc
  - Symphony No. 3 in F Major, op. 90 - Brahms, 12/20/1942; hupka_3126; Rehearsal?; VinylDisc
  - Symphony No. 3 in F Major, op. 90 - Mvt. I - Brahms (conc.), 2/20/1948; hupka_3423; Studio 8-H; Test; Dress rehearsal; Broadcast on 02/21/1948; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 3 in F Major, op. 90 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (conc.), 2/20/1948; hupka_3425; Studio 8-H; Test; Dress rehearsal; Broadcast on 02/21/1948; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 3 in F Major, op. 90 - Mvt. IV - Brahms (Pt. 1), 2/20/1948; hupka_3424; Studio 8-H; Test; Dress rehearsal; Broadcast on 02/21/1948; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 4 in A Major (Italian), op. 90 - Mvt. I & III - Mendelssohn, 3/12/1949; hupka_2655; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 4 in A Major (Italian), op. 90 - Mvt. II & IV - Mendelssohn, 3/12/1949; hupka_2652; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 4 in A minor, op. 63 - Mvt. I - Sibelius (Part 2), 5/22/1940; hupka_3491; Record # 050837-1R; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 4 in A minor, op. 63 - Sibelius (starts w/ announcement from Victor pressing); Un Ballo in maschera - Verdi, 4/27/1940; hupka_0466; Ballo - rehearsal; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60 - Beethoven, 11/4/1939; hupka_1851; 043548-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 11/4/1939; hupka_1852; 043549-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60 - Mvt. I - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 11/4/1939; hupka_1853; 043550-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/4/1939; hupka_1836; 043551-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 11/4/1939; hupka_1839; 043552-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60 - Mvt. II - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 11/4/1939; hupka_1840; 043553-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60 - Mvt. III - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 11/4/1939; hupka_1841; 043555-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/4/1939; hupka_1842; 043556-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60 - Mvt. IV - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 11/4/1939; hupka_1843; 043557-1; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 29 in A Major, K. 201, Piano Concerto No. 27 in B flat Major, K. 595, Le Nozze di Figaro - Overture - Mozart, 12/5/1943; 9/3/1944; hupka_0113; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 31 in D (Horn call) - Haydn, 10/29/1938; hupka_0725; "Note: The opening bars of this copy have accidentally been erased - could be corrected from repeat; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 31 in D Major (Horn Call) - Haydn, 10/29/1938; hupka_0130; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mozart, 11/2/1946; hupka_2670; Rehearsal; Sides 2 & 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3039; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3041; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3043; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3047; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3049; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3051; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; cracked in half; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. I & IV - Mozart, 11/2/1946; hupka_0721; Rehearsal; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. I; Zauberflöte - Mozart, 11/2/1946; hupka_0723; Rehearsal; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. II & III - Mozart, 11/2/1946; hupka_0722; Rehearsal; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. IV - Mozart, 12/5/1943; hupka_3037; From O.W.I. Record; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 & The Magic Flute - Overture - Mozart, 11/2/1946; hupka_2671; Rehearsal; Sides 1 & 3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 35 (Haffner), K. 385 & Divertimento in B flat, K. 287 - Mozart, 11/2/1946; hupka_2669; Rehearsal; Sides 5 & 7; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mozart, 11/6/1946; hupka_3211; 4-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mozart, 11/6/1946; hupka_3212; 3-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt III & IV - Mozart; Die Zauberflöte, 11/2/1946; hupka_0061; "Haffner" - Rehearsal; Transferred w/ Grado from lacquers on 10/23/1983; Test tape; FREE; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. I - Mozart, hupka_2945; D6-RC-6440-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. I - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3112; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Disc 3; CD on EC; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. I - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3114; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Disc 3; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. I & II - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3113; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Disc 4; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. I & III - Mozart, 11/1/1946; hupka_3111; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Disc 4; CD on EC; Shellac disc
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. II - Mozart (conc.), hupka_2969; D6-RC-6442-3A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. II - Mozart (Pt. 1), hupka_2957; D6-RC-6441-3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Symphony No. 35 in D Major (Haffner), K. 385 - Mvt. III - Mozart, hupka_2983; D6-RC-6443-2; Lacquer discs/acetates